Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Records MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Activities, 1978-2012; 49.6 Linear Feet in 38 record cartons, 15 oversize folders, 7 cassette boxes, 5 flat boxes, and 4 manuscript boxes.; 26 U-matic; 20 Hi8; 17 MiniDV; 5 VHS; 1 Betacam; 1 Betacam_SP; 2.87 Megabytes in 123 files.
  - Subseries II.A: Programming, 1978-2004
    - Useful statistics, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
    - War on Drugs / Columbia show, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - World Bank 50 Years -- Cathy and May Ying's folder, Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - World Trade Center show logs, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Xeroxes of production photos, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Yugoslavia, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Yugoslavia -- Clippings and notes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Yugoslavia -- Materials, Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Yugoslavia -- Notes and logs, Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Video Dial Tone -- Credits, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Subseries II.B: Exhibits and Installations, 1985-2011
    Subseries II.B Exhibits and Installations (1985-2011) includes records relating to Paper Tiger TV's participation in and organization of exhibits, both in the U.S. and internationally. These records include exhibit ephemera such as flyers, brochures, and posters; planning documentation such as proposals, correspondence, timelines, budgets, and floor plans; and video recordings used in installations.
    Subseries II.B Exhibits and Installations (1985-2011) is arranged alphabetically.
    - 30th Anniversary Exhibition, New York University, 2009-2011 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Anthology Installation -- Compilation Tape, undated (Box 116, Vhs 276_0733)
    - Art in General - Video Marathon, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Berkeley Art Museum & Pacific Film Archive - residency, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Bluestockings Women's Bookstore forum, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Brandalism, Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - "Bronx Stories" Event, Bronx Museum, May 20, 2011 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Catalog galley - negative, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Commitment - Toronto exhibit, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Copy Shop installation brochure (Germany), 1992 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Desktop Theater - proposal, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Dream House exhibit, Wexner Art Center, 1991-1992
      - Betacam recording, August 1991 - January 1992 (Box 80, Betacam 276_0403)
      - Comments, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Crankee master -- Dub A, undated (Box 147, U-matic 276_0981)
      - Electronic records, 1990-1991; FA_MSS_276_ER_9
      - Floorplans, Undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Furniture certificates, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Hi8 recording, undated (Box 188, Hi8 276_1579)
      - Hi8 recording, undated (Box 188, Hi8 276_1580)
      - Installation plaque, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Remove passage, September, 1991 (Box 188, Hi8 276_1581)
      - "Women of the Scarlet and Gray" calendar, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Working file, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Exit Art - The First World Exhibit, Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Govett-Brewster Art Gallery, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Guerrilla Girls Review the Whitney exhibit, the Clocktower, May 17, 1987
      - Tape 1 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0338)
      - Tape 2 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0344)
      - Tape 3 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0340)
      - Tape 4 (Box 76, U-matic 276_0342)
    - Hnads On! at UC Berkeley Art Museum and Pacific Film Archive, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Hands On! exhibit flyer, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - "I've Been Framed" exhibit - Anthology Film Archive, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Information Libre - media timeline, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Information Libre - timeline and posters, Undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Installation - Cologne (German material), 1992 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Installation - Contemporary Art Gallery, Van Couver, Canada, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Installation - equipment, Undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Installation - furniture plans, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Installation - furniture plans (crankee wall), Undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Installation - list of things and equipment, Undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Keep on Livin' - at the Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Kunstpassage - Munster installation posters, 1986 (Folder 35)
    - Malcolm X Community Organizing Academy - Events, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Media Mogul March -- Images, 1997-1998; FA_MSS_276_ER_10
    - Media Mogul Trip, undated (Box 181, Minidv 276_1176)
    - Museum of Modern Art, New York, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Mythos Information - Welcome to the Wired World exhibition, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Narrowcasting and the Rise of the Religious Right - Installation comments, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - "A Need for Space" - Columbus Art League Exhibition newsletter - Dream House review, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - News Stand Publications - AIDS: The Artists Response, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - News Stand Publications - And Then, 1982, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - News Stand Publications - The Anti-Warrior, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - News Stand Publications - Australian Society, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - News Stand Publications - Billboard Liberation Front, Undated (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - News Stand Publications - Bohemia (spanish), 1990 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - News Stand Publications - Borderlines, 1985-1989 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - News Stand Publications - Carrie: The Magazine that can Move Things, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - News Stand Publications - Center for Exploratory and Perceptual Arts, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - News Stand Publications - Centro, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - News Stand Publications - City Limits, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - News Stand Publications - Contemporary Arts Press Distribution, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - News Stand Publications - Copwatch, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - News Stand Publications - Cups: a Cafe Journal, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - News Stand Publications - El Diario (spanish), 1991 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - News Stand Publications - Dropout, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - News Stand Publications - Ear Magazine of New Music, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - News Stand Publications - Economic Notes, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - News Stand Publications - Extra!, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - News Stand Publications - Filth, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - News Stand Publications - Forbes (modified), 1984 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - News Stand Publications - Foreign Language newspapers, mixed, Undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - News Stand Publications - Future Survey, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - News Stand Publications - Gai Pied Hebdo (french), 1992 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - News Stand Publications - Ground Work, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - News Stand Publications - Hallwalls, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - News Stand Publications - Huffbo Chente, Undated (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - News Stand Publications - Huracán, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - News Stand Publications - Indigenous Peoples' Network, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - News Stand Publications - The Intermeddler, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - News Stand Publications - International Indian Treaty Council, Undated (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - News Stand Publications - International Telecommunication Union, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - News Stand Publications - Internazionale IDOC, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - News Stand Publications - The Journal of Bizarre Occurrances and Ridiculous Deaths, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - News Stand Publications - Kill for Peace (Tuli Kupferberg), 1987 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - News Stand Publications - Kumira (Myrna D. Bain), 1985 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - News Stand Publications - Labor History, vol.32, #5, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - News Stand Publications - Left Business Observer, 1991, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - News Stand Publications - Link Timor, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - News Stand Publications - Links: Health and Development Report, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - News Stand Publications - Lookout! #37, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - News Stand Publications - Memo, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - News Stand Publications - The Mill Hunk Herald, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - News Stand Publications - The Missing Link, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - News Stand Publications - Mixed flyers and mailers, Undated (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - News Stand Publications - Monk, Undated (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - News Stand Publications - Monthly Review, 1987, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - News Stand Publications - Movement Research Performance Journal, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - News Stand Publications - Los Muchachos, Undated (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - News Stand Publications - Muckraker, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 35)
    - News Stand Publications - National Catholic Reporter, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - News Stand Publications - New Indicator, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - News Stand Publications - The New Internationalist, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 36)
    - News Stand Publications - A New World, #12, 13, Undated (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - News Stand Publications - Off Our Backs, 1989, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - News Stand Publications - Our Sister, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - News Stand Publications - Pangloss Papers, Undated (Box 85, Folder 38)
    - News Stand Publications - Political Affairs, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 39)
    - News Stand Publications - Processed World, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 40)
    - News Stand Publications - The Progressive Review, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 41)
    - News Stand Publications - PSR Monitor, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 42)
    - News Stand Publications - Punch, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 43)
    - News Stand Publications - Questionable Cartoons (Tuli Kupferberg), 1981 (Box 85, Folder 44)
    - News Stand Publications - Quirk's Reviews, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 45)
    - News Stand Publications - Radio Homerun, Undated (Box 85, Folder 46)
    - News Stand Publications - Rain, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 47)
    - News Stand Publications - Red Balloon, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - News Stand Publications - Red Bass, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - News Stand Publications - El Rescate, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 48)
    - News Stand Publications - San Francisco Art Institute Viewbook, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 49)
    - News Stand Publications - Sex and Politics, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 50)
    - News Stand Publications - A Short Course in Cable, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 51)
    - News Stand Publications - Skeptical Inquirer, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 52)
    - News Stand Publications - Slingshot, 1990 (Box 85, Folder 53)
    - News Stand Publications - Socialist Review, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 54)
    - News Stand Publications - Stars amd Stripes, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - News Stand Publications - Street Sheet, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - News Stand Publications - The Thistle, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - News Stand Publications - UFT Bulletin, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    - News Stand Publications - Unesco Boletin, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 55)
    - News Stand Publications - The Upright Ostrich, 1990-1991 (Box 85, Folder 56)
    - News Stand Publications - Video Guide, Undated (Box 87, Folder 26)
    - News Stand Publications - Visions, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 57)
    - News Stand Publications - Voices of the Twentieth Century, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 58)
    - News Stand Publications - Witness for Peace Newsletter, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 59)
    - News Stand Publications - World Policy Journal, Undated (Box 85, Folder 60)
    - News Stand Publications - Youth Outlook, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 27)
    - News Stand Publications - Z Magazine, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 61)
    - News Stand Publications - Z Papers, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 62)
    - NO-TV and Movies exhibition, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Non-Stop - Germany exhibit, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - "Not An Alternative" Installation, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Open House, 2002, undated
      - Tape one -- Al-Amir, Raquel, Jen, October 12, 2002 (Box 187, Minidv 276_1549)
      - Tape two -- Group 3, Michael, Garret, Kerri, undated (Box 187, Minidv 276_1557)
      - Manuel, Chika, Evelyn, undated (Box 186, Minidv 276_1512)
    - Paper Tiger House, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Paper Tiger on the Prown at the Eye Gallery, San Francisco, Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Paper Tiger TV Installation, undated (Box 151, Vhs 276_1636)
    - Paper Tiger TV - Timeline boards, Undated (Flat-file-folder 6, Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4)
    - "Paper Tiger Television Re-Presents the Media" Installation, Ramapo College, November 4-27, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Plaque explaining use of crankees, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Printed Matter - alternative and corporate media timelines, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Printed Matter - extra and duplicate quotes and photo credits, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Proposals, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Paper Tiger Television Re-Presents the Media" Installation, Ramapo College of New Jersey, November 4-27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - "Roar" boards - originals, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 8-10)
    - Rutgers exhibit - comment cards, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco Art Institute - installation brochure, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco Art Institute - "Paper Tiger TV Smashing Myths..." exhibit, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - "Surveilling Surveillance" Interactive Projects and Q&A, Think Coffee, undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Stencils, Undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Television Delivers People Exhibit, Whitney Museum of American Art, 2007-2008 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Video exhibitions - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Videowall exhibit, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "Whitney" and mixed, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Whitney exhibit - floor plan, Undated (Box 35, Folder 10, Folder 32)
    - Whitney exhibit -- Mailing list and sign-in book, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Whitney exhibit - screening schedule, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - "Women of the Scarley and Gray" calander comments, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Subseries II.C: Workshops and Conferences, 1985-2012
    Subseries II.C Workshops and Conferences (1985-2012) contains records relating to Paper Tiger TV's participation in and organization of workshops and conferences.
    Paper Tiger facilitated many filmmaking workshops, particularly with youths in the New York City area, on the subjects of equipment training, documentary filmmaking, editing software, and media literacy. Paper Tiger also regularly attended professional conferences in the field of public access media, such as National Alliance for Media Art and Culture (NAMAC) Confernences (1985-2000), the Media Consirtium (1991), the Media and Democracy Conference (1997), the Allied Media Conference (2003), and the Being the Media: Designing a New Rrradical Media Conference (2012). They also attended and captured footage of organizing conferences in the sphere of the political left, such as the Socialist Scholars Conference (1997-1999) and the Left Forum (2009).
    Files for these events include ephemera, such as schedules, flyers, and posters; planning documentation, such as curricula, outlines, meeting notes, and educational resources; and video recordings of event proceedings.
    Subseries II.C Workshops and Conferences (1985-2012) is arranged alphabetically.
    - A16 DC Workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Access for All, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Alberta College - Public Talks and Screenings poster, Undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Allied Media Conference, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - AMC Workshop outline, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Anti-military recruitment poaster, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Art Lab Workshop, Columbus Museum of Art, 2012 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - "Being the Media: Designing a New Rrradical Media" Conference, New York City, February 10-11, 2012
      - Paper materials (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Presentation recording (Box 186, Minidv 276_1515)
    - Bookmobile Project, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Breaking Walls, Building Bridges - conference poster, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Breaking Walls, Building Bridges - youth conference, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Brecht performance - Berlin, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Brooklyn Friends - day workshop, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Brooklyn Friends School - Media Literacy Workshop, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Burlington Workshop, undated (Box 82, Hi8 276_0450)
    - Class Dismissed - workshop evaluation sheets, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Class Dismissed - workshop - online lesson plan examples, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Class Dismissed - worshop series, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Class Dismissed - workshop series, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Committee leadership training, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Community Access goes Digital, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Community Media Leadership Institute conference, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Crash Course on the Collective Process, 2011 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Curriculum Development workshop / Youth workshop meeting notes, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 27A)
    - Cyberspace Workshop, undated
      - NYNEX -- Part 1 (Box 72, U-matic 276_0276)
      - 2600 Interview and NYNEX -- Part 2 (Box 71, U-matic 276_0273)
      - Quote...Unquote, Move 1620, Rape of Dr. Willis (Box 71, U-matic 276_0270)
      - Willamina Cooke (Box 72, U-matic 276_0274)
      - Hi-8 recording (Box 82, Hi8 276_0442)
    - DC workshop -- Rome's tape, undated (Box 82, Hi8 276_0451)
    - "Defeat Rising Fascism in Defence of the Black Nation" conference poster, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Demo Against Media, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Diversity training / race workshop, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Documentary Workshop Curricula, undated (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Educational Video Center - workshop materials, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Fenced Out workshop - outline, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Fierce / NNZ at Cypher, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Fierce / NNZ at Cypher, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Final Cut workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Final Cut workshop - editings, PTTV evaluations, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Final Cut workshop - Final Cut Pro, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Final Cut workshop - Final Cut Pro handouts, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Final Cut workshop - Final Cut Pro workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Final Cut Pro Editing Workshops, 2003-2007 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Freeing the Media - Teach in / Speak out, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - "Freeing the Media" poster, Undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Gender Roles workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Goddard College Summer Program, Undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Green Chimneys - research, waivers, and logs, Undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Green Chimneys - youth outreach, Undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - "The Gulf War and the Renewed Rise of Racism" Discussion, Sam Anderson, Learning Alliance, undated (Box 82, Hi8 276_0443)
    - Gulf War Rally - flyers, Undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Hands On! Youth, Media, and Activism after Seattle - workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - "Hands off Cuba" video summit, Undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Independent Features conference, Undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Independent Teach-In / Speakout, The Learning Alliance, 1996; FA_MSS_276_ER_11
    - Invoices file - Drums Asian Working Class Women and Girls workshop, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Jean Zine - Lower East Side Girls Club - made at PTTV workshop, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - "Labor, Race, Housing, Prison, and War - with Oligopoly cards, Undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Learning Tech Fair, Undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Learning Tech Fair - workshop, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Left Forum, 2009, undated
      - Crisis as Solution, Tape one, April 18, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1601)
      - Crisis as Solution, Tape two, April 18, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1602)
      - Culture and Industry, Tape one, April 18, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1032)
      - Culture and Industry, Tape two, April 18, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1031)
      - Long Term Strategies, Tape one, April 18, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1597)
      - Long Term Strategies, Tape two, April 18, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1596)
      - Nationalize the Banks, Tape one, April 19, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1600)
      - Nationalize the Banks, Tape two, April 19, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1595)
      - RTTC, 2009 (Box 189, Minidv 276_1030)
      - Childhood Capitalism Panel, Tape one, undated (Box 189, Minidv 276_1014)
      - Childhood Capitalism Panel, Tape two, undated (Box 189, Minidv 276_1018)
      - Interviews, B-Roll, undated (Box 189, Minidv 276_1016)
    - Legal Issues for Filmmakers workshop, Undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Manhattan Neighborhood Network - youth initiated channel, Undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Media Alliance Conference -- "Influencing Social Policy," Cornell University, October 26, 1990 (Box 188, Hi8 276_1571)
    - Media Arts - NAMAC conference, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Media Consortium, February 11, 1991
      - Tape one -- Navasky (Box 180, Hi8 276_1049)
      - Tape two -- Media cam (Box 180, Hi8 276_1045)
      - Tape two (Box 181, Hi8 276_1062)
    - Media and Democracy Conference, October 16, 1997
      - Evening session, Media Moguls protest (Box 82, Hi8 276_0448)
      - Thursday evening, Hightower (Box 82, Hi8 276_0449)
    - Media Network Conference -- bell hooks on Clarence Thomas Hearings, undated (Box 184, Hi8 276_1329)
    - Middle East Conference, Cooper Union -- Master edit, undated (Box 74, U-matic 276_0311)
    - Military Myths - APSC's Counter Recruitment training manual, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Military Myths - Articles and Ads, Undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Military Myths - Changing America, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Military Myths - classroom curriculum, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Military Myths - curriculum, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Military Myths - endorser agreements, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Military Myths - evaluations - screenings and flyers, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Military Myths - Interview contacts, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Military Myths - Jen with Roots workshop notes, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Military Myths - Jen to do (feedback), Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Military Myths - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Military Myths - outreach, correspondence, evaluation forms, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Military Myths - pamphlets, workshop material, curriculum, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Military Myths - press releases and questionaire, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Military Myths - Related events, partner organizations, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Military Myths - Release forms for interviews, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Military Myths - Roots (binder), Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Military Myths - Roots workshop, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Military Myths - Roots schedule, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Military Myths - screening locations, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Military Myths - stats and alternatives, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Military Myths - Stats, recruitment and anti-recruitment material, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Military Myths - workshop summary, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous seminars, research, lectures, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - NAMAC conference, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)